<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_ACCESS_TO_PLUGIN">Access to the tools plugin</string>
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_ACCESS_TO_PLUGIN_DESC">Members of this role have access to the Tools plugin</string>
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_DESC">Tools recognized the following plugins:\n\n</string>
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_ENABLE_SUBPLUGINS">These settings allow you to enable or disable subplugins. (Default: all subplugins enabled)</string>    
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_INFO1">Tools is a platform for smaller Admidio plugins (sub-plugins).\n\nAll sub-plugins must be in subfolders of tools and have the same name as the subfolder. Example: .../Tools/user_info/user_info.php. By default, a button is generated for each detected sub-plugin, which can be used to start it.</string>    
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_INFO2">During installation, a menu item and an access role are automatically created for the main script Tools.\n\nHowever, a separate menu entry can also be created for each sub-plugin.\n\nIf, for example, you only need the sub-plugin USER_INFO from the tools collection, the following URL entry is required in the menu:\n\n/adm_plugins/Tools/user_info/user_info.php</string>     
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_INFO3">It is strongly recommended to specify a role for each menu item under "Visible for". Both tools and the sub-plugins create an access permission from the specified roles.</string>   
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_INSTALL_UPDATE_REQUIRED">The existing installation is incomplete. It is necessary to run the installation routine again.\n\nTo install, run the following script: #VAR1#</string>
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_NAME">Tools</string> 
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_NAME_DESC">The Tools plugin</string>
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_PLUGIN_DATE">Status</string>
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_PLUGIN_NAME">Plug-in name</string>
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_PLUGIN_VERSION">Version</string>
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_SUBPLUGINS">Subplugins</string>         
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_UNINST_ACCESS_ROLE_ERROR">- An error occurred while deleting access roles. Not all access roles could be deleted.\n</string>
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_UNINST_ACCESS_ROLE_SUCCESS">- The access roles created by the plugin have been deleted.\n</string>   
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_UNINST_DATA_DELETE_ERROR">- An error occurred while deleting the configuration data.\n</string>
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_UNINST_DATA_DELETE_SUCCESS">- The configuration data created by the plugin has been deleted.\n</string>
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_UNINST_MENU_ITEM_ERROR">- An error occurred while deleting the menu item.\n</string>
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_UNINST_MENU_ITEM_NOT_DELETED">- The menu item created by the plugin could not be deleted because it is still in use in another organization..\n</string>
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_UNINST_MENU_ITEM_SUCCESS">- The menu item created by the plugin has been deleted.\n</string> 
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_UNINST_NO_INST_IDS_FOUND">- No menu item and/or access role could be found. You must delete the menu item and access role manually..\n</string> 
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_UNINST_SECURITY_CHECK">Are you sure you want to uninstall the plugin?</string> 
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_UNINST_STARTMESSAGE">The following deletions were performed:\n\n</string>
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_UNINST_TABLE_DELETE_ERROR">- The table "adm_plugin_preferences" could not be deleted because it houses more data from other plugins.\n</string>
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_UNINST_TABLE_DELETE_SUCCESS">- The created table "adm_plugin_preferences" was deleted.\n</string>
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_UNINSTALLATION">Uninstall</string>
    <string name="PLG_TOOLS_UNINSTALLATION_DESC">Entries created by the plugin can be deleted via uninstallation.</string>
</resources>